<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ourlaska</title>
    <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ourlaska</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Powered by the [Newsprint Theme](https://themes.gohugo.io/newsprint/) for [Hugo](https://gohugo.io/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 14:30:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ourlaska.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>McCarthy: big rivers, big glaciers, big mountains</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/4_mccarthy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 14:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/4_mccarthy/</guid>
      <description>Glaciology Summer School Every second year, an International Summer School in Glaciology is held in McCarthy (see Map further below). A summer school typically consists of a series of lectures, exercises and field excursions concentrated over a couple of days in a certain location, to give a deep introduction into a specific research field to graduate students. The summer school in McCarthy is unique in many ways: the location is literally thousands of kilometers away from any other University (out of Alaska), the students are simply camping for 10 days in a remote place without running water, and the lectures are held in a cozy block hut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrival in Fairbanks: twilight and huge wilderness</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/3_alaskatwilightsurface/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 14:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/3_alaskatwilightsurface/</guid>
      <description>Twilight in Fairbanks Here we are, Fairbanks Alaska! When we land at the Fairbanks International Airport, it is around one in the morning. Although the sun has set since a couple of hours, it is not completely dark, it is twilight and it will stay like this until the sun will rise again around 4.00 am. This is already quite interesting for us. Back in Zurich, we wondered how it will be without darkness at night, and now that we are experiencing it, it feels quite exciting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Switzerland and crossing Schweizerland</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/2_leaving_switzerland/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/2_leaving_switzerland/</guid>
      <description>Every travel-adventure starts with packing How does your luggage look like when leaving your home for two years and your new domicile is on another continent, with an ocean in between? To start with, do we actually have enough suitcases? Thanks to Anna&amp;rsquo;s cousin Michela and her family we were provided with a sufficent number of baggages (they are really great, Michela!). Nevertheless, our belongings must be condensed to what is essentially needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna and Pascal</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/1_anna_and_pascal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 11:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/1_anna_and_pascal/</guid>
      <description>Who we are We are Anna and Pascal, an Italian-Swiss couple ready to leave Europe for a while. We are both geoscientists and met at the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology - ETH Zurich, where we both recently completed a PhD. Anna focuses on the transport of sediment in alpine rivers, Pascal investigates debris-covered glaciers. Also if you are not interested in what river bring transport or you never saw a glacier: in this blog you will find nice pictures and hopefully interesting information on these topics and other amazing places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>