<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ourlaska</title>
    <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ourlaska</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Information wants to be free [Stewart Brand, 1984]</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:30:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ourlaska.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Switzerland and crossing Schweizerland</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 11:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/post2/</guid>
      <description>Every travel-adventure starts with packing How does your luggage look like when leaving your home for two years and your new domicile is on another continent, with an ocean in between? Your belongings are greatly condensed to what is essentially needed. Regarding our final destination close to the Arctic Circle, our limited luggage space was dominated by things we related to a rather cold and rough climate: warm jackets, shoes, pants, socks, blankets etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready to go</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 01:59:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post2/</guid>
      <description>Here is where everything started! On May 20th we left Rutschwil, a wonderful village &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna and Pascal</title>
      <link>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 11:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ourlaska.github.io/post/post1/</guid>
      <description>Who we are We are Anna and Pascal, an Italian-Swiss couple ready to leave Europe for a while. We are both geoscientists and met at the Swiss Federal Institute of Technology - ETH Zurich, where we both recently completed a PhD. Anna focuses on the transport of sediment in alpine rivers, Pascal investigates debris-covered glaciers. Also if you never saw a glacier: in this blog you will find nice pictures and hopefully interesting information on these and other amazing places.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>